Protecting the Earth from the scum of corporate America.
The Big One is a documentary film directed by Michael Moore.
The Big One is an investigative documentary from director Michael Moore who goes around the country asking why big American corporations produce their product
abroad where labor is cheaper while so many Americans are unemployed, losing their jobs, and would happily be hired by such companies as Nike.
Self, played by Michael Moore.
Self, played by Jim Czarnecki.
Self - Random House Media Escort, played by Elaine Bly.
Self, played by Brian Danitz.
Self - Innocent Guy, played by Richard Jewell.
Self (archive footage), played by Bill Clinton.
The Big One is a 1997 documentary film written and directed by documentarian
filmmaker and activist Michael Moore, and released by Miramax Films.
The film documents Moore during his tour promoting his 1996 book Downsize This!
around the United States.
Through the 47 towns he visits, Moore discovers and describes American
economic failings and the fear of unemployment of American workers.
The film explores themes of prison, airport, narration, protest, ohio.